Tom Stine

Web3 Developer and Web3 Advocate-Instructor

Springfield, Missouri USA tomdev@13z.one

Github: https://github.com/13zebras

SKILLS

Technical skills: Web3 and NFT projects with _Buildspace using Solidity, JS, and React on Ethereum, Polygon, and Solana. React + HTML/CSS/JS. Linux/Bash/Zsh. Experienced teacher in a wide variety of subject areas, ages 14-70+, online and in person. Video production and editing for a wide variety of uses. Excellent writing and public speaking skills. Photo editing with Photoshop & GIMP.

EXPERIENCE

Center for Talented Youth / Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, MD - *Math Teacher* AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

Teaching Algebra 1 online to gifted students..

Study Alternative High School, Springfield, MO - Teacher, Advisor, JAG Specialist AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2021

- Taught math and courses for Jobs for America's Graduates Program at Study.
- Managed a student-run t-shirt business, The Study Printing Emporium.

LAUNCH Online Education, Springfield, MO - Math, Earth Science, ACT Prep JANUARY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

• Taught online courses to students from around Missouri.

Tom Kornbluh, Consultant - Course Content Creator & Website Development APRIL 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Developed online consultant training program; write content; create lessons and videos.
- Used Wordpress and PHP for website.

Springfield Public Schools, Springfield, MO - Substitute Teacher (part-time)
NOVEMBER 2015 - MAY 2017

Personal Development Website, Springfield, MO - Writer, Developer, Marketer MAY 2009 - SEPTEMBER 2011

- Created & developed website focused on life coaching & personal development.
- Developed Instagram, Facebook, and Twitter for online marketing; learned PHP, HTML, CSS, Ecommerce, Wordpress; enhanced skills at writing and presentation; video production and editing.

Day Trading Stocks, Commodities, and Forex, Springfield, MO - Self-employed

FEBRUARY 1997 - JANUARY 2015

• Trading of forex, futures, options, stocks, and bonds.

Bailey Alternative High School, Springfield, MO - Classroom Teacher

MARCH 1994 - FEBRUARY 1997

- Taught math, science, health, workplace & computer skills, service learning, reading. Daily advisory group, counseling, life skills.
- Designed and managed computer lab, provided building-wide tech support.

Professional Massage Training Center, Springfield, MO - Anatomy Instructor

APRIL 1994 - NOVEMBER 1995

Missouri State University, Springfield, MO - Botany Lab Instructor

AUGUST 1992 - MAY 1993

ITT Financial Services, Springfield, MO - Assistant Manager, Lending

MAY 1991 - MAY 1992

Carol Jones Realtors, Ozark, MO - Real Estate Salesperson

OCTOBER 1987 - JANUARY 1990

EDUCATION

Web3 Training, Projects, and Courses, Online

JUNE 1992 - JULY 1994; JANUARY 2000 - AUGUST 2002

- Buildspace.so: web3 projects including NFTs, smart contracts, Solidity, React frontends.
- Moralis Academy: Courses on Ethereum smart contracts, Contract Security, Solidity, etc.

Missouri State University, Springfield, MO - Teacher Certification

JUNE 1992 - JULY 1994; JANUARY 2000 - AUGUST 2002

Courses for Missouri Teacher Certification in biology, chemistry, physics, and math. Additional graduate coursework in Counseling.

Brown University, Providence, RI - BA Biology, magna cum laude

SEPTEMBER 1983 - MAY 1987

Primary coursework in molecular biology, biochemistry, and neuroscience. Broad range of humanities courses with particular interest in American history.

Ozark High School, Ozark, MO - Diploma

SEPTEMBER 1979 - MAY 1983